{
    "subject": "resource/Deborah_Meaden",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/City_College_Brighton_&_Hove",
    "human_readable": "Deborah Meaden attended City College Brighton & Hove.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9872717261314392,
            "question": "Is Deborah Meaden associated with Brighton & Hove City College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9851757287979126,
            "question": "Did Deborah Meaden graduate from City College Brighton & Hove?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9776796698570251,
            "question": "What is known about Deborah Meaden's time at City College Brighton & Hove?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9737356305122375,
            "question": "Name the college that Deborah Meaden attended."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9684478640556335,
            "question": "Which City College did Deborah Meaden attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9472429156303406,
            "question": "Where did Deborah Meaden attend college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6344105005264282,
            "question": "What type of institution is City College Brighton & Hove?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5699794292449951,
            "question": "Can you describe Deborah Meaden's educational background?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5504019856452942,
            "question": "What are some possible fields of study offered at City College Brighton & Hove?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49311649799346924,
            "question": "What institution of higher learning is associated with Deborah Meaden?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Deborah Meaden attended City College Brighton & Hove.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6719_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some possible fields of study offered at City College Brighton & Hove?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6719_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe Deborah Meaden's educational background?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6719_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of institution is City College Brighton & Hove?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6719_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6719_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain information about Deborah Meaden's educational background, which includes attending Godolphin School and Trowbridge High School. However, they also mention that she went to Brighton Technical College after leaving school at 16, which implies that she attended City College Brighton & Hove (formerly known as Brighton College of Technology)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Deborah Meaden received an Honorary Graduate Award from her old college, which is identified as City College Brighton and Hove. Therefore, the triple stating that Deborah Meaden attended City College Brighton & Hove is supported by the information provided in the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}